Jeff Lupinski

Digital Designer Denver, Colorado hello@jefflupinski.com +1 303 345 1962 Portfolio <sup>7</sup> LinkedIn <sup>7</sup>

I am a designer with experience spanning visual design, product, UX/UI, and art direction. For over a decade, I have collaborated with brands ranging from Fortune 100 to non-profits and start-ups.

## Selected Experience

### Freelance Independent Designer

#### May 2012 - Present

Partnered with agencies including Instrument, Huge, Handsome, Ueno, and Use All Five. Client work Marriott Bonvoy, Google, Salesforce, Epic Games, Chubb, Liquid Death, and Specialized Bicycles.

## Senior Designer at BASIC / DEPT

## July 2022 - Aug 2024

Designed interactive experiences, interfaces, and digital products for enterprise clients, including Google, Ocean Spray, Nike, and Taco Bell. Partnered closely with cross-functional teams to align on objectives, present design concepts, and ensuring smooth handoffs for efficient implementation.

#### Senior Designer at Handsome

## Aug 2020 - Jul 2022

Contributed to the full design lifecycle of digital experiences for clients like 7-Eleven, FedEx, Meta, and AMC Television. Led design projects, worked with stakeholders and cross-disciplinary teams to define, visualize, and execute product visions that aligned with client goals and enhanced user engagement.

#### Senior Designer at Pluralsight

### May 2018 - Mar 2020

Led the design and creative direction in developing, refining, and implementing a comprehensive company-wide design system and brand identity for GitPrime. After the 2019 acquisition by Pluralsight, oversaw the integration of GitPrime's design language into Pluralsight's broader ecosystem.

# Product Designer at MojoTech

## Oct 2014 - Jul 2018

Created end-to-end product designs from wireframes to coded solutions. Collaborated with product owners to translate complex requirements into intuitive and user-friendly interfaces for both web and mobile applications—ensuring alignment with business goals and technical constraints.

#### Education

# Bachelor of Science, Graphic Design and Digital Media Johnson and Wales University, 2008 – 2012

Graduated with Honors Cum Laude

Skills

Visual Design	Interaction Design	Product & App Design
User Interface (UI) Design	User Experience (UX) Design	Design Direction
Presentation Skills	Deck & Guideline Design	Project Management
Wireframes & Prototyping	Front-end Development	Team Collaboration
Design Systems & Libraries	Strong Attention to Detail	Responsive Web Design

## Technology

Figma, Adobe Creative Suite, Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects, InDesign, Sketch, Framer, Principle, Webflow, Origami, Keynote, Al Tools, InVision, Frame.io, Slack, Trello, Asana, HTML, CSS, JavaScript